Guide to the Department of Athletics, Yale University, Records Documenting Softball
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Department of Athletics, Yale University, records documenting softball
1981-1998
RU 994
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
0.5
(1 box)
The records consist of scorebooks, minutes, and reports documenting softball at Yale University.
Yale University. Dept. of Athletics
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 38-B (YRG 38-B), Records documenting specific sports at Yale.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The materials were transferred from the Department of Athletics, Yale University, 2005.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the materials is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by topic.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of scorebooks, minutes, and reports documenting softball at Yale University.
College sports; Softball; Yale University -- Sports; Yale University. Dept. of Athletics
- Softball team records, 1960-1998; Accession 2006-A-110
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2023
  - Official NCAA Baseball/Softball Scorebook, 1998 (Box 1)
  - Score Book
    - 1960-1964 (Box 2)
    - 1965-1967 (Box 3)
    - 1981 (Box 1)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 1)
    - 1983 (Box 1)
  - General Administrative, 1981-1986 (Box 1)
  - Softball Association, 1987-1988 (Box 1)
  - Varsity Budget, 1985 (Box 1)
  - Varsity Post Season, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Varsity Recess, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Reports, 1982 (Box 1)
  - Publications, 1982-1989 (Box 1)